Valeriia Rieznik



Contact

Address:

Kharkiv

Phone:

+38(066)9988247

Portfolio:

https://valeriia-rez.github.io/Portfolio/

Email:

valeria09122016@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/valeriia-ri eznik-a8310b195/

Gihub:https://github.com/Valeriia-Rez

Knowledges

Html5/Semantic Markup, Responsive Web Design, Css3/Flex-box, Sass/BEM, Command line, GIT/NPM, JavaScript/ES5/ES6+, Bootstrap, Webpack(familiar), Babel(familiar), Agile(trello board for planning work), Adobe Photoshop.

Personal Skills

Motivation.Energetic.

Team player. Confident, friendly and easy to get along with.

Passionate about doing a good job. Handling criticism well and learning from it.

Work under pressure and to tight deadlines.

Summary

I am a highly motivated and ambitious personality with a strong communication skills and learning abilities. While working in the banking sector, I learned how to work with a large amounts of information, think logically and work in a team as well as take initiative in my hands. However, after 10 years of work at the bank, I realized that I want to challenge myself even more. For that, I had to got out of my comfort zone. Over the past couple of years, I have noticed a great increase in technology and various online platforms. It seemed to me that programming could become a very interesting and rather challenging profession that I could master. Just in a week of self-training and viewing various video courses, I realized that programming offers great opportunities in the world of technology. Despite all the skills that I have developed in the banking sector and those that I acquired during self-training, I understand that there is still a long way to go, but I have got enough dedication and passion to become a successful developer.

Experience

Portfolio - https://valeriia-rez.github.io/Portfolio/(all personal projects you can find in my portfolio).

EPAM Training (December 2019 - March 2020).

During the training period I improved my knowledges in such topics - HTML, CSS, Preprocessors, CSS Layouts, Responsive Design, JS(control flow, functions, data types,scope & context), DOM, BOM. I learned how to collaborate with others and how to work in a team on a various projects. I have built around 10 projects including a few big ones such a SPA(single page application) and E-Commerce-Website in vanilla JS using ES6 classes and interacting with a DOM api.

Course Modern JavaScript From The Beginning (November - December 2019 Udemy

https://www.udemy.com/course/modern-javascript-from-the-beginning).

The Complete JavaScript Course: Build Real Projects (November 2019 Udemy

https://www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-javascript-course).

Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, Animations and More (October 2019 Udemy

https://www.udemy.com/course/advanced-css-and-sass). CSS Course (September 2019 itproger.com). HTML Course (August 2019 https://htmlacademy.ru, htmlbook.ru, itproger.com).

These are just some of them that I went through.

Lead Economist Ukrsibbank (2016 - Present). Kharkiv Region, Ukraine.

- Re-conducting and primary identification of Individuals, individuals-entrepreneurs and legal entities
- Opening and closing accounts for Individuals, individuals-entrepreneurs and legal entities.

Leading Specialist in Cash & Banking Operations Ukrsibbank (2010-2016). Poltava Region, Ukraine

- Cash Operations
- Opening / closing / execution and maintenance of current, deposit and card accounts of individuals and legal entities in national and foreign currency;
- Receiving and sending money transfers
- Document control

Banking Cashier-Operationalist PJSC Poltava bank (2009-2010). Poltava Region, Ukraine

- Cash Operations
- Currency exchange
- Utility payments

Education

Ukrainian Academy Of Banking Of The National Bank of Ukraine. Bachelor's degree, banking(2004-2009).

Language

English - B1